National Women's Health Network records SSC.MS.00360
Sophia Smith Collection
- 2019-S-0005, 1976-2015; 9.167 linear feet (11 containers)
  - NWHN policies, 1975-2013 (Box 250)
    - Leave policy, 1999 March (Box 250)
  - Board of Directors, administration, 2000-2014 (Box 250)
    - Board committees, 2012-2013 (Box 250)
    - Conflict of Interest forms, 2008-2014 (Box 250)
    - New committees, 2010 (Box 250)
    - Board development resources, 2005-2006 (Box 250)
    - Board member job description, 2001 (Box 250)
    - 25th Anniversary fundraising, 2000 (Box 250)
    - The strategic board process, 2002 (Box 250)
  - Board Chronological files, 1996-2011 (Box 250)
    - Executive Director evaluation, 2015 (Box 250)
    - Board Committee - ad hoc thank you, 2011 April (Box 250)
    - Board Committee - ad hoc board development, 2010-2011 (Box 250)
    - Board correspondence, 2006 (Box 250)
    - Board poll, 2006 April (Box 250)
    - Board poll, 2005 October (Box 250)
    - Board poll, 2002 (Box 250)
    - Ashcroft poll, 2001 January (Box 250)
    - Board poll - Leonare Tiefer, 2000 (Box 250)
    - Board Poll, 1999 November (Box 250)
    - Board poll - personnel policies, 1996 December (Box 250)
    - NWHN Board recruitment packet, 2003 (Box 250)
  - Board Correspondence, 1992-2005 (Box 250)
    - Board Correspondence, 1992-2005 (Box 250)
  - Miscellaneous Board History, 1978-2003 (Box 251)
    - Board committee responsibilities, 1988-1992 (Box 251)
    - Statements of former board members, 1978-2000 (Box 251)
    - Board of Directors membership contests, 2001 June (Box 251)
    - Bylaws, 1979-1986 (Box 251)
    - Infertility newsletters, 1990-1993 (Box 251)
    - Old Board and leadership lists, 1984 (Box 251)
    - Board Conflict of Interest, 1999-2002 (Box 251)
    - Board job descriptions, 1999-2001 (Box 251)
    - Board effectiveness ad hoc committee, 2002-2003 (Box 251)
  - Stategic Planning, 1998-2003 (Box 251)
    - Strategic Planning process, 1998-2003 (Box 251)
    - Management Assistance Group, 2002-2013 (Box 251)
    - Strategic Framework, 2003 (Box 251)
    - Management Assistance Group consulting process, 2003 (Box 251)
  - Internship Program, 2003-2011 (Box 251)
    - Internship program history approximately, 2003 (Box 251)
    - Intern Orientation Manual, 2011 (Box 251)
  - Cynthia Pearson Personnel, 1991-2016 (Box 251)
    - FDA 101 Spring, 1993-1994 (Box 251)
    - Calls with Board Chair, 2015 June - 2016 May (Box 251)
    - Calls with Dora (Board Chair), 2012-2013 (Box 251)
    - Calls with Bindiya (Board Chair), 2008-2011 (Box 251)
    - Cynthia Pearson Worry list, 2003-2015 (Box 251)
    - Cynthia Pearson's Board Meeting notes, 1996-2012 (Box 251)
    - Notes on transition meetings, 1996 May (Box 251)
    - Correspondence from old interns / volunteers, board, founders, 1991-1995 (Box 251)
  - Cynthia Pearson Conference Files, 2006-2010 (Box 251)
    - APHA, 2010 (Box 251)
    - Consumers United For Evidence-Based Healthcare, 2010 (Box 251)
    - ORWH 20th Anniversary Conference, 2010 September 27 (Box 251)
    - Women Deliver, 2010 (Box 251)
    - Maryland Women's Coalition Healthcare, 2010 June 5 (Box 251)
    - Critical Perscription Skills, 2010 May 12-14 (Box 251)
    - New NIH WH Research Agenda, 2010 March 22 (Box 251)
    - Wellesley College Quantative Reasoning for Women's Health, 2010 February 25 (Box 251)
    - Families USA Health Action, 2010 January 1 (Box 251)
    - Illinois Campaign for Better Healthcare, 2009 November 18-19 (Box 251)
    - APHA Philadelphia, 2009 November 7-11 (Box 251)
    - OWH Conference, 2009 July 16-17 (Box 251)
    - Surgeon General's Meeting, 2009 March 19 (Box 251)
    - IOM Committee on Women's Health Research, 2009 February (Box 251)
    - APHA San Diego, 2008 October 25-29 (Box 251)
    - NOW Conference, 2008 February 19 (Box 251)
    - NIH Microbicide Meeting, 2008 July 18 (Box 251)
    - Ford Convening, 2008 April 30 (Box 251)
    - Funders Network on Population, Reproductive Health, and Rights, 2008 March 13-14 (Box 251)
    - UWISC Med Women's Studies, 2008 March 1-4 (Box 251)
    - APHA, 2007 (Box 251)
    - NWHAT meeting, 2006 July (Box 251)
    - UHCAN meeting with women's group, 2007 May 24 (Box 251)
    - UCSC Health Fair, 2007 February 14 (Box 251)
    - NCL presentation on HT, 2007 January (Box 251)
    - APHA menstrual suppression talk, 2006 (Box 251)
    - APHA Boston, 2006 November 4-8 (Box 251)
    - Briefing on Women's Health (implants), 2006 March 3 (Box 252)
    - NIH Conference Cesarean on Request, 2006 March 27-29 (Box 252)
  - Cindy Pearson policy files, including policy reports, 2008-2011 (Box 252)
    - BCA / Barbar Brenner CP Farewell, 2011 (Box 252)
    - Correspondence, 2011-2014 (Box 252)
    - HERvotes, 2011-2012 (Box 252)
    - Manmog Screening USPSTF, 2009 November (Box 252)
    - OBOS/NWHN general history, 2003-2007 (Box 252)
    - Obama election - pro choice principals meeting, 2008 November 12 (Box 252)
    - Reproductive Health meeting with Obama transition team, 2009 December (Box 252)
    - Goals / Accomplishments, 2010 January (Box 252)
    - Program reports for government updates, reports, etc., 2015 (Box 252)
    - Program reports for funders, etc., 2013 (Box 252)
    - Thank you letters, 1993-2005 (Box 252)
    - Intern Orientation & Resource Manual, 1992 (Box 252)
    - NWHN Perspectives, 1996-2005 (Box 252)
    - National Women's Health Networks Website, 2003 (Box 252)
    - Clearinghouse Packet guidelines, 2012 (Box 252)
    - Website timeline, 2003-2004 (Box 252)
    - NWHN Website redo, 2003 (Box 252)
    - Chorel meeting notes, 2015 (Box 252)
    - Vaginal Health: Douching Petition, 2003 (Box 252)
    - Sterilization Abuse, 1982 (Box 252)
    - Douching AAWE advocacy, 2003 (Box 252)
    - Tampon Safety, 1999 (Box 252)
    - Weight & Fitness, 1989-2003 (Box 252)
    - Diet drugs, 1999-2007 (Box 252)
    - Weight/Fitness: diet drugs FDA, 2000 October 4 (Box 252)
    - Wyeth v. Levine (pre-emption), 2008 (Box 252)
    - Riegel v. Medtronic Inc., 2007 August 27 (Box 252)
    - NWHN Publications, 1980-2012 (Box 252)
    - NWHN Policy positions as recorded, 1990 (Box 252)
    - New member welcome, 1991 (Box 252)
    - Acquisition Packages, 2000-2004 (Box 252)
    - Abortion Poster, 2015 (Box 253)
    - Updates & Lapsed Mail Campaigns, 2007-2011 (Box 253)
    - Appeal Campaigns (General & Major Donors), 2003-2016 (Box 253)
    - Intern Event Reports, 2009-2012 (Box 253)
    - Website redesign, 2015 (Box 253)
    - Member thank you letters, 1997-2007 (Box 253)
    - NWHN Intern Orientation Manual, 2007 (Box 253)
    - Health Requests, 2010 (Box 253)
    - Health Requests - Phone & additional docs used to answer, 2011 (Box 253)
    - Intern / Volunteer Alumni Network, 1990-1998 (Box 253)
    - Computer floppy disks 43: Cynthia Pearson / Beverly Baker / Grant docs / Position papers / Perspectives, 1991-2006 (Box 254)
    - Computer floppy disks 43: Cynthia Pearson / Beverly Baker / Grant docs / Position papers / Perspectives, 1999-2001 (Box 254)
    - Computer floppy disks 43: Cynthia Pearson / Beverly Baker / Grant docs / Position papers / Perspectives, 1996-2006 (Box 254)
    - Computer floppy disks 43: Cynthia Pearson / Beverly Baker / Grant docs / Position papers / Perspectives, 1996-1999 (Box 254)
    - Computer floppy disks 43: Cynthia Pearson / Beverly Baker / Grant docs / Position papers / Perspectives, 1994-2004 (Box 253)
    - Backup disk: Administrative computer / Cynthia Pearson's computer, 1992-1998 (Box 253)
    - Computer floppy disks: two unidentifiable (Box 253)